var questions = [{
    "question" : " aaaaaaaaaa?",
    "option1" : " Abacus", 
    "option2" : " Aus", 
    "option3" : " Abus", 
    "option4" : " Abus", 
    "option5" : " Abus", 
    "option6" : " Abus", 
    "answer": "2"
}, {
    "question" : " bbbbbbbaaa?",
    "option1" : " Abacus", 
    "option2" : " Aus", 
    "option3" : " Abus", 
    "option4" : " Abus", 
    "option5" : " Abus", 
    "option6" : " Abus", 
    "answer": "3"
}, {
    "question" : " cccccaaaaaaa?",
    "option1" : " Abacus", 
    "option2" : " Aus", 
    "option3" : " Abus", 
    "option4" : " Abus", 
    "option5" : " Abus", 
    "option6" : " Abus", 
    "answer": "1"
}, {
    "question" : "dddddaaaaaaa?",
    "option1" : "Abacus", 
    "option2" : "Aus", 
    "option3" : "Abus", 
    "option4" : "Abus", 
    "option5" : "Abus", 
    "option6" : "Abus", 
    "answer": "1"
}, {
    "question" : " eeeeaaaaaa?",
    "option1" : " Abacus", 
    "option2" : " Aus", 
    "option3" : " Abus", 
    "option4" : " Abus", 
    "option5" : " Abus", 
    "option6" : " Abus", 
    "answer": "3"
}, {
    "question" : " ffffaaaaaaa?",
    "option1" : " Abacus", 
    "option2" : " Aus", 
    "option3" : " Abus", 
    "option4" : " Abus", 
    "option5" : " Abus", 
    "option6" : " Abus", 
    "answer": "1"
}, {
    "question" : " gggaaaaaaa?",
    "option1" : " Abacus", 
    "option2" : " Aus", 
    "option3" : " Abus", 
    "option4" : " Abus", 
    "option5" : " Abus", 
    "option6" : " Abus", 
    "answer": "1"
}, {
    "question" : " hhhaaaaaaa?",
    "option1" : " Abacus", 
    "option2" : " Aus", 
    "option3" : " Abus", 
    "option4" : " Abus", 
    "option5" : " Abus", 
    "option6" : " Abus", 
    "answer": "4"
}, {
    "question" : " iiiiaaaaaaa?",
    "option1" : " Abacus", 
    "option2" : " Aus", 
    "option3" : " Abus", 
    "option4" : " Abus", 
    "option5" : " Abus", 
    "option6" : " Abus", 
    "answer": "5"
}, {
    "question" : " jjjjaaaaaa?",
    "option1" : " Abacus", 
    "option2" : " Aus", 
    "option3" : " Abus", 
    "option4" : " Abus", 
    "option5" : " Abus", 
    "option6" : " Abus", 
    "answer": "1"
}]





// $("#button1").click(function (event) {
   
//     window.location.href = "questions.html";

//     });